http://www.englishgardeningschool.co.uk/privacy-policy

Your Personal Data
We will hold and process your personal data and information provided by you for contractual and/or legitimate reasons.  Therefore, personal data may be shared with and between third parties namely our tutors, consultants, suppliers and lecturers, other students or alumni as reasonably necessary for the students’ educational course and EGS business.  EGS ensures appropriate security of the personal data that it holds, including protection against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss.
Right to Deletion
You have the right to request that all your personal data we hold is deleted by contacting us in writing, where we will confirm deletion or if not possible, explain the legitimate or lawful reasons why such a request cannot be actioned.
Right to Rectification
You have the right to request that we amend any personal data we hold for you if you believe it is incorrect, by contacting us in writing.
Subject Data Access Request
You have the right to request confirmation of the actual personal data we hold for you and how this has been processed, by contacting us in writing.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, requests or a complaint about how we hold or process your personal data, then please contact us
by post to EGS Enterprises Ltd, Sandhill Farm House, Nyewood Road, Rogate GU31 5HU
by email to me or info@englishgardeningschool.co.uk
If you think that your data has been misused or is not being kept secure, you should contact EGS Enterprises as listed above.  If you are unhappy with its response or need any advice, you should contact the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO).
+44 (0)20 7352 4347
The English Gardening School © 2013
|| Privacy Policy || Web design by The Indigo Concept
